Contact 9756720259 saddamhusain975672@gmail.com Skills extrusion operator Visa & citizenship Nationality Indian System generated resume by

foundit

Saddam Husain

2D Animator | Ahmedabad

Summary

i am saddam husain extruder operator in production mixing machine experience grinding machine installation 8 yreas experience. MFI qaulity control experience in GMP certified company iso 1900_2015 .and kaizen &5s safety roles 3m (muda .mura.muri)

Not a job hopper

Experience

2D Animator

tekniplex India - Jan 2022 - Present . 2 Yrs 1 Mos.

Production - Jan 2022 - Oct 2022 . 8 Mos.

Production - Sep 2015 - Jan 2022 . 6 Yrs 3 Mos.

extrusion operator - Jan 2022 - Oct 2022 . 8 Mos.

Extrusion Operator

production - Jan 2022 - Oct 2022 . 8 Mos.

Responsibilities

extrusion operator in production department.and mixing department.my job profile is the best performed with push bawnding, hard working in future.

Education

Bachelor of Arts (B.A), Other Arts

2015 - H. N. B. Garhwal University (HNBGU)